

Javier Olivieri

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER Y UX/UI DESIGNER

I am a Wordpress Developer with extensive experience in the design, implementation and administration of said CMS. I have great communication skills, I am detailed and creative. I enjoy working as a team and keep myself updated with the latest trends in the IT industry.

CONTACT

 \bigvee

coderjav@gmail.com



Cel: 1169658937



linkedin.com/in/coderman

ACADEMIC TRAINING

- Pharmacist, Buenos Aires' University, 2012.
- Front End Developer, Coderhouse, 2022.
- Full Stack Developer, Coderhouse, 2022.
- Ux/Ui Design, Coderhouse, 2022.
- Neurolinguistic Programming, Capacitarte, 2023.

OTHER KNOWLEDGE

- Html, Css, JavaScript, Php, Sass, Git,
 Github, Responsive Design, Bootstrap,
 Netlify, Vercel, Localwp, Git Bash, Google
 Font, Visual Studio Code, Xampp, Postman,
 Google Analytics, PixelYourSite, Facebook
 Pixel.
- Figma, Behance, Elevator Pitch, Userflow, Usability, Accessibility, MVP, Whimsical.

LANGUAGES

• Intermediate English language

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Wordpress developer & UX/UI Designer

Maxirest, March 2023 - Present.

- Wordpress site development (Elementor, Wp Bakery, APIs, Multisite, Login by Token).
- Development of custom plugins for Elementor and Wp Bakery.
- Implementation of agile methodologies (Scrum). Jira management.
- Development of prototypes in Figma.
- Chatbot implementation on Wordpress sites (Aivo).
- Remote work environment through GitHub repositories.

Web Developer, Wordpress

Decimo Technology Solutions (Costa Rica), March 2022 - March 2023.

- Development of sites in Wordpress (Elementor, Wp Bakery, Custom).
- Constant communication with clients, to carry out the design.
- Development of promotional coupons for the GSK laboratory (Honduras, Costa Rica, Guatemala).
- Websites maintenance.
- Set up advertising and SEO campaigns.

Wordpress Developer (Front and Back)

Freelance, June 2021 - present.

- WooCommerce development.
- Translation of sites into several languages.
- Construction with Elementor, Wp Bakery, Divi.
- Search engine optimization.
- Hosting.
- · Site security.